Hello, you are watching Civil Business.
I hosted Aram Mkhitaryan, the group's
regional head for Central Asia and the Caucasus, and the
head of Yandex Armenia.  Hello.
Hello.   Thank
you, Aram, for accepting the invitation
.  Aram, just by introducing yourself, a
question arises, right?
We understand Yandex Armenia, we know that you
are the head of Yandex Armenia.  Then there was
information in the press a few months ago
that you were also appointed as the regional head of the Yango Group for
Central Asia and the Caucasus. Yango Group has
nothing to do with Yandex. Explain this connection a little bit.
Then let's move on. The group is a
very good one.
It is a large technology company with its
headquarters in
Dubai.
We work [in]
about 35 countries
around the world, if I'm not mistaken. We are talking
about the Asian markets of Latin America, Africa, and Asia, as well as about the Asian countries, with the
difference that if in the main
markets we work
using our main brand,
in the Asian countries we still continue to
work directly under the Yandex brand.
That is, the group uses the Yandex
brand in the CIS countries.
Yes, Yandex Armenia. Yandex Armenia
is part of the group
and provides the services that, by and large, are
offered by Yandex. I'm right,
not necessarily, because different
countries have their own
list of services, they differ significantly from each other,
and if we look at the two countries
About markets like I don't know Armenia and
Georgia, you can see that there are
certain services that
operate in Georgia, certain
services operate in Armenia, it
's clear, one of the main services is
always the locomotive taxi, so to speak
right-handing.
But
no, I mean it's
provided from the list of services that
Yandex has,
those technologies used the
technologies
that Yandex has, but
we have many services that were
originally created and appeared
exclusively in international markets.
For these specific markets, for example,
what service?
For example, we have the service
that originally started in the
Emirates, in the
United Arab Emirates it is a
service that is designed for [soul]
rental car aggregators
.  At the moment, it is available in the CIS countries
, if I'm not mistaken, in
Kazakhstan, and a week ago
we also launched it in Georgia.
Oh, very good, Aram.  The
volume of services that you provide to Armenia, first of all, before
moving on to that,
I can't help but ask about the relationship between the Group and Andex, let's clarify a little
and move on, yes the group
was created, I'll ask directly yes, so that
Yandex doesn't suddenly appear in
Yandex services that you provide in
other countries
outside of Russia yes, so that you avoid sanctions,
because you are a partner in appearing under sanctions,
or did this start earlier? I
think there are two thoughts that I
will express, which will put everything in its
place, so to speak. First, since it is a
Russian company, the
Andex company as such has never
been sanctioned,
and second, the group was created
well before 2022
and specifically to be presentable in international markets in a
different way.
And why was it not possible to be present with Yandex?
Look, the markets are very significantly different from
each other, starting from
how people pronounce the brand
name and how much they sew,
ending with the approaches, because we are
trying to see, there is one important thing  The
so-called home market
concept is
one thing,
but in new countries
we were first of all associated
with taxis, a high-
tech company, and we needed a brand with a new, more
youthful,
newer approach,
which was created in time, and that was long
before 22.
So, let me say that the ultimate beneficiary of the group is the
Russian parent company, I
mean where the income generated by the group is
ultimately accumulated,
where does the group go?
It is a company that has an
appropriate
structure. In the overall structure, there are
simple ones,
that is, it has shareholders, non-stakeholders,
shareholders who
are their shareholders.
As far as I know, not
shareholders, so I will say this so that we do
not use the English word, very well, in Armenia, the
volume of services that Yandex
provides. First,
what are the leader services, and second,
approximately what volume of transactions are you talking about? I
can mention that almost all of our
services that we
provide  and at the moment there
are about 13 of them in Armenia.
We
are the market leader in all services.
Of course, as in other similar markets, our
locomotive is taxi as a
service.   I
can give you a few numbers to give you an
idea of ​​the size of the company.
If we take the
total amount of services transactions that exist in our Armenia
, it makes up
1.2 to 1.3% of Armenia's GDP, 3% of the
GDP,
that is, you
make up about that much of the economy of Armenia.
Yes, that is the total amount of our transactions.
What about the jobs we create,
that is, if I'm sorry, if it's about
30 billion in Armenian
dollars, you can
imagine approximately what volume we are
talking about.
As for jobs, I can
say and note that
about 10% of the active population of Armenia
earns money somehow
through our platforms, about
10% of the active workforce, how many taxi drivers,
so to speak, taxi drivers,
you have
tens of thousands of registered taxi drivers, tens of thousands of
drivers, of course, there is an important
difference here. Look, we have active
drivers for whom this work is the
main job, the
main job, and we have, let's
say in English, part-time employees,
not employees, drivers,
who
also perform and provide non-
regular passenger transportation
services to earn extra money.  Let
's look at the total, we
are talking about more than 100,000 people.
The labor force in Armenia is more than 100,000. I mean, I'm
sorry, I should also add that we are not talking
about drivers providing direct transportation, we are talking
about couriers, we are talking
about new jobs that have emerged as a result of delivery and food services. For
example, they are order pickers.
We say 100,000 workers.
Yes, but the main part is of course a large proportion.
They are taxi
drivers. It's understandable. It's quite a
large number. In that
regard, in terms of services, you
said you are in the leading positions.
You provide 13 services. The main one,
of course, is the taxi service. You are in the
leading positions. In terms of this
anti-monopoly
struggle, what position are you in from the point of view of
relations with the relevant commission? Are
n't you close to
having a monopoly position in the market?
We have a dominant position in the market, which is
already a
fairly big responsibility
for us, and also a certain
How does the Commission for the Protection of Economic Competition look at it? The
Commission for Competition and Consumers is in
constant contact with us. We
are under constant monitoring. I would like to
note that we also have a
corresponding working group established and
we are constantly carrying out joint
work. Over the past year, a
fairly large volume has been included
in these works.  I can give a few
examples of the
results we have achieved.  First, for example, I
think you know that the price of a trip is
determined by dynamic pricing, because
there are cases when demand is much
greater than supply, in which case a
special mechanism for dynamic
pricing operates.
The price is going up.
Yes, the price rises in order to
ensure that supply meets the demand that
exists.   We have
made several significant changes to the example in that section
.  First, if the
current price is more than twice as high as the base price
, we
do not charge our commission for the excess amount and
give drivers the opportunity
to earn more money,
meaning if, for example, the regular price should have
been 1,500 drams and it is 3,500 drams at that moment,
you will not receive your commission.
No, we already charge a commission of more than twice the amount of 500 drams
, that is, we had a
base price of 1005
drams. I'm explaining this roughly, but if
that delta is more than double, which is
more than double, we
no longer charge our commission in that part.
Uh-huh.   In
that part, of course, there are always quite a few questions about
how that
pricing occurs, and as
a result of the work done by the same working group,
we have also made changes
to my satisfaction. You can
see the price gap at any time,
why the price is the way it is at the moment, what the
base tariff was, the
mileage, the time,
yes, in the application you can click
yes and see the entire gap, even as a
result of dynamic pricing,
how the price
has changed as a result of high demand, so that we can be as transparent as possible.
Several other significant
changes have been made for drivers.  The first one
concerns our+ service.
The sand is our washing
program.   At the
moment,
if we talk about the price of the order, the
price of the order that
the passenger sees and the price of the order that the
driver sees are already identical
and the organization has taken the entire part of that discount on
itself in the
form of cashback, they no longer
receive bonuses, that's
not a pro, it's like it was provided by the driver before,
that discount is
taken entirely by the organization.
And the commission has increased due to that,
we have reduced the commission in the economy tariff as
a result of that working group, the economy year start tariff is a celebration, how much is the
commission?
14,
and already in the comfort and comfort plus
segments it is higher, it is
higher, I do
n't remember exactly, but I think it is about 17%,
about 17%, see as a user of your
services, it often happens that there are
different opinions, drivers complain, they say that
Ordex takes very high
commissions and even say
that Ain Chvoi's so-called, so-called
tips,  He says that you leave it in exchange for the service
, that's where the
commission fee comes from
and says that for every good service I
provide, I get paid, and that's unfair from the driver's
perspective at this point.  What do you
say?
First of all, what is true is that
tips are
not charged at all
and are completely transferred to
the driver. I should mention that this has been the case from the beginning.
And that's how it happened.  Why are they like that? Well,
it's already a matter of the mentality and I
don't know the approaches of our drivers. Did you get it?
[snorts] That's it.
What about them? The
percentages are high. Look, the same
competition commission constantly
conducts comparative analyses in similar
markets as a result of monitoring. It's similar services. What kind of
commissions do they have? Do we have any good ones?
That is, we
are constantly under monitoring. And since I
think the population of Armenia knows very well what kind of commissions their
friends in the United
States of America pay, and they bring them back, which are
several times
higher. I
think it's not very fair to
make such statements. Because
our commissions are one of the lowest in the region. The
average driver in the comfort+ segment who
works for you, the taxi driver, if he is a
permanent employee, that is, he doesn't work directly
after work.
How much money can he
earn on average per month?
First of all, I would like to note that neither the drivers nor the
delivery drivers are
employees of our company.
are individuals who
provide services
to other individuals through our platform, that is, in fact,
if we take your example, when
you order a taxi, our platform
as a market finds another appropriate
individual who is ready to
provide that service to you.  That is,
we are talking about their income,
we have an analysis
for the past year and in the tariff plans you mentioned,
we are
talking about an average gross income of about 300,000.
That is an average income.
Because sometimes, I
ask taxi drivers myself, just to be
interested, they say a higher number,
that they have constructive earnings.
That is an average number. I am telling you, there were
also complaints about the tax
that taxi drivers paid. At the
same time, some taxi
drivers also say that they do not mind
paying, they pay, but they want to
receive certain things from the state in return, if they
pay taxes to the state themselves, then they should
receive, for example, insurance, have the
opportunity to receive, I don't know,
some options for income tax refunds.
What discussions are there
with the state in this regard?
First, I would like to explain how the
systems sector currently works,
because starting in September 2024,
a new system has been introduced as a result of cooperation with the state, as
a result of which
we and other platforms like us
are already tax
agents
and automatically make deductions from
drivers and transfer them to the
state.  The point is that
if we are talking about the taxi sector,
that is,
we are talking about non-regular passenger transportation
, because taxi service
as such is
regulated differently.
As a rule, a
5% state tax is withheld from the price of each trip for cash payments and a
4.5% state tax for non-cash payments.
Here I would like to note that the system
is completely automated, meaning that
when the driver registers in the system,
thanks to the existing integration between us and the company, if the driver does not have a
HHN, we generate
and provide the HHN accordingly. As a
tax agent, we automatically make
all deductions, which means that
the driver does not need to submit a tax
report on his income.
That is, online HDM is generated.
Yes, you can go to
your history of purchases in
the application at any time and see the generated HDM
coupon. This is a completely automated
system. I can say that in the last two
years, that is, in 2004,
we invested in it in September. Two years have passed. We have
already collected about 8 billion state
taxes. We are currently
trying to implement a similar process and a similar reform in the delivery
sector.
Draft amendments to the laws
are underway.  We very much hope that from
January 2027 this
will also be included as such.  And if we talk
about what kind of complaints and
wishes there were related to that payment
,
yes, drivers have constantly voiced
and are still speaking of
complaints regarding the fact that we pay a
fee, they consider it a tax, even though it is a
state fee,
and drivers have a desire to be
able to receive
certain other social
benefits under the taxes paid, one of which is mandatory
medical insurance. We were also
talking
about pension payments and other things like that,
because this is not so much in our field, it is
more in the field of the state.
During the past six months, there have been
quite extensive discussions, and
the state has already taken certain steps in the
field of mandatory healthcare, and
drivers should be included in the
framework of these mandatory insurance services.
Here, I would like to mention one important thing:
very often, drivers do not
realize that all the
wishes they have,
if we project this on the
employee of any company, we are
talking about about 25 to 30% of the tax.
about paying.
And in that case they receive those good things,
those social benefits, but I
think that's in the state's field.  We
are providing as much necessary information as possible so that
the state can act accordingly.   As
a result of this reform, nothing has
changed: at the moment, any driver
who works through platforms
can also apply to the local tax authority
, receive a certificate, use that certificate
to be able to get a
loan, present the certificate to
the embassy to receive a visa, etc.
Yes, so they have certain advantages in
this regard.
Very well, look, periodically, I won't say
regularly, but videos appear on our internet
about problems between drivers and customers, sometimes there are
conflict-generating or conflict-inducing
situations.  First, in that case,
who can people turn to when such
questions arise, because very often
they simply make them public to
resolve these issues, and second,
because the client cannot
call anyone, as far as I know, there is a bot in Yandex, to which you
write or
someone from there answers or the bot
responds to you, why don't you have a
hotline like this, which you can call? And second, is there
any control over the selection of drivers
or
not, because very often we hear
that there is no control,
anyone, at any time, it doesn't matter what that person's
past has been, what he has now, he
can register and work for you.
Look, if we're talking about the
current, unknown, and ongoing
status of drivers, we only allow
drivers who have the right to do so by law to work on this platform
.
Uh-huh.  Yes,
that is, he
has a driver's license, if he has a
driver's license, then he has undergone
appropriate inspections, etc., etc.,
that is, we work
within the legislative framework that exists in the
Republic of Armenia,
that is, you do not conduct additional inspections
.
We do not conduct additional checks
, because, as I repeat, we
are a platform that
transfers the order of one individual to another
, but I consider it
necessary to mention that we have
control mechanisms in place
that help us
completely remove problematic drivers from
the system.
I would also like to point out that
if we disconnect
a driver from the system, as such, he or she
can never return and work in the system.
Yes.
Of course, we have different blocking
options, but I always
urge in all my speeches
and I urge again that
one of the most so-called influential tools is
evaluation, because the system
is automated in most cases, in the case of several
negative ratings, it
is definitely evaluated by a special system, an analysis is performed,
and if necessary,
the driver is blocked.  Unfortunately, our mentality does not always
allow our passengers to
make that assessment, because if I
put it in colloquial language, there is always that, well, the
person keeps house, something, oh,
I am not an employer, etc., it is not allowed, I
think it is unacceptable, because
if we want to pay for the
service,
if we pay, of course, you see, there are
problems and drivers and
passengers are very, very different types of people. The
important thing to remember is that both the driver and the
passenger are the same people who came from the bosom of our people.
Very often, the same
driver can appear in the passenger
seat. For us, both the passenger
and the driver are users of our system.
Yes,
we treat both equally.
Yes, both are registered. We
provide service to both as a
market plus.
Regarding these complaints, I again urge you to
rate as high as possible. In case of low ratings,
the system will always ask you additional questions
to clarify what the
problem was.  As for the call
center, look, it's an accepted practice around the
world.  You can see the same, let's
take an example, we do
n't even have that call center, because
the volume that there is
cannot be served by phone calls. In
case of any problem, you need to write to
our help center. Do
you have users in Armenia, that is, people
who use your service? We are
talking about Yandex.Go or <> we are
talking about all our services, in
this case, taxi services.
If we are talking about Yandex.Go, we
are talking about about 1 million people,
which is not every day, but I
understand that there are 1 million
active users per month, and the monthly active users
are 1 million people. If we are talking
about all services in Armenia, then
1-3 million per month,
that is, you really have a taxi
service near you.
You see, Yandex Go is not just a taxi,
Yandex Go includes taxis,
food, delivery, etc., right?
We work on a principle
called super app, huh? That is, super
app, huh
super app, which allows
a person to solve their everyday
problems.
I understand
Aram. It is not a concern for you as a
company from the point of view of competition
that you do not have an equivalent competitor in Armenia. I
mean, a roughly similar
competitor that occupies the same position
in the market and would be in very tough competition with you.
This does not contain
elements of stagnation. It does not
contain problems for the company.
Look, they
will provide similar services. We have been working in the
Armenian market for exactly 10 years.
This year marks our tenth anniversary
in Armenia.
During these 10 years, there have been many
different companies, as well as
international companies,
that have tried to enter. There has been
competition, there has been struggle.
We always look at competition very positively.
As a manager, I
only [snort]
see the positive in competition.
That is, the market is open.
If there are certain companies, but
also international companies that are
interested, I think you
see that local companies
appear, they have a certain part of their market. I
think
a few a year.  Similar products always
appear.
Look at that,
but why can't they survive properly? I
can't say that,
I can't give an assessment for them. I'm
not saying it from your perspective as a market participant.
What is the problem with your success? What is the reason for
their failure?
I can say one important thing: you see,
we are a large technology company,
regardless of the fact that we are often
associated exclusively with taxis, but
taxis are just one of our services
.  Look, if
your service is the most popular
in Armenia, at least that's why they
associate it.   It
's the first service.  Look, if we
look at some older markets, let's
talk about the same Yandex as a search
engine,
it was originally created as a power
system,
its biggest business model is
advertising,
so if we compare it
with Google, it
started from about the same point in 1997 and
you are the main one in the Russian-speaking segment
and if we talk about the company
, but for
example, look,
our geo-services also play a very important role in all this, I
think I can
proudly say that geo-services,
geo-services include
maps and navigator.
At the moment, we have the highest quality data in Armenia.
And since we are the ones who are
responsible for maintaining this quality
, so to speak, in our maps
and we are proficient in graphs, that's a bit of a
technical term in maps, we are
able to provide the best possible
service based on our
geodata.  In other words,
we bring the car closer as quickly as possible, so
we can correctly calculate what kind of
traffic jams there are in the city at the moment, in other words,
how do you see the traffic jams, sorry?
It's a very simple mechanism, look,
I'm asking a simple question, but
still, it
's a very simple mechanism.
At the moment, the navigator is still being used,
if I'm not mistaken, more than 700,100,000
people are active.
Any navigator that works
also provides feedback completely
anonymously, what is the average speed
compared to the accumulation of phones
, that's right.
Yes, yes, that is, we know that
for example, the capacity of a given
road, a given street, not
the capacity, but the permitted
speed is 60 km/h, but we
see that at the moment five devices are moving at 10 km/h on that
street.
This means that
machine learning models
work
quite sophisticatedly.  By the way,
last year, if I'm not mistaken,
we made an innovation in maps, and it's
very possible that you and two of your
friends could open the same navigation app from point A to point B
, and ask it to create a
route.  We'll tell one person, for example,
five minutes, tell another, six minutes, for example,
why? Because you have different driving
habits, one drives faster, one
drives slower, so
these machine learning models are also
your driving
habits.
In other words, if someone tries to experiment
and walk around the streets of Armenia, Yerevan, for example, with
100 phones, they can
fool the navigator.  I understand correctly.   The
models have an anti-frost system
and can see for themselves.  I don't think it would be
possible to move at car speed.
They saw a similar social advertisement for it.
No, it's not that easy, because all
such systems have anti-fraud
tools.
In other words, you can't create problems.
You see,
during the war, that topic was especially
relevant, because they said, for example, that people from abroad
could call or order taxis,
100-150 taxis at once in one place, and
create traffic jams in the city,
create problems, riots, etc., etc.
First of all, is there a danger or not, because there has
n't been such a problem during this time, as far as I
know, why was there such a
rumor circulating, or is it just from the
realm of rumors? It's just from the
realm of rumors.
People in general are always inclined to these
conspiracy theories and
spreading such rumors.
Any big company, I'm talking about
really big companies,
not small ones,
all technologies as such
have anti-fraud
mechanisms like this.
It's
always under constant monitoring. It's possible to do something like this on
big platforms. People often
complain about it, sometimes they tell us about it.
For example, I don't know about something.
You can talk to your friend about something.
Open Facebook. If you
see an ad about it. Open Google. You
can see some material about it.   They
say they hear us.
Yandex is listening to us, Alisa is listening to us
.
Alice doesn't listen, and I can also tell you,
you can, if you're interested,
Alice also has a special module built into it, a
separate module
that physically turns off the microphone.
That is, when you say Alisa,
she physically turns it on.
Uh-huh.
In other words, it is necessary to connect in the event of that instruction.
There is a special module installed on the level of
Aliyev.
Well, since we've already talked
about data, how reliably is our data
protected and
stored with you?
Look, the data is about
100,000 citizens
.
When we talk about data,
we're talking about two things:
data transfer and data storage
.  Our company
applies the
principle of logical isolation of data storage,
that is, the data of
passengers or users of the Republic of Armenia, let me say this, are stored
logically, or rather, the
word "logical" may sound a little different in
Armenian, separately from
users of other countries.
This allows us to exclude
all possible risks.
That is, Yandex 30, I don't know in this case,
Yango Group 30
provides services in different countries,
stores the
personal data of all countries separately, personal data, it
is clear, there can be work
data that has nothing to do with personal
, they should be combined with
your work internal data, our internal data,
so that the system works, but we are
talking about personal data,
personal data, card data
can be, it can be
movement data, etc.,
pictures, etc., etc., so in our
case, a picture, a picture of the driver, a picture of the passenger,
all that data
is stored in separate repositories by country and
one country does not have the opportunity to receive it from another country, they are
stored on your servers, I
understand correctly, yes
[clears throat] I
understood,
people also use it to
see the buses, I don't know
where public transport has reached, what it has
done, and in the conditions of our traffic jams, it
is especially relevant, but sometimes we see
a situation where you can
look in Ads, that a specific bus, a
specific bus number, I don't know 10  It's going
to be approaching in a minute, and then you see
that it's standing at the bus stop at that moment,
huh? First of all, how do you track,
that is, follow
public transportation? Are you connected to
that system, aren't you? Or is
there just some kind of periodicity and frequency that you've set up to
automate that car and that's how they
come and approach, how does that happen?
As for transport, as
a result of our cooperation
with the Yerevan Municipality, we receive
data from the Yerevan Municipality on all
buses, trolleybuses, and if I'm not
mistaken, even
minibuses already have GPS devices installed on them.
The data is collected and
processed exclusively
by the Yerevan Municipality, and the data
necessary for that movement and
calculation
is provided to us, as a result of which we already
show it in Yandex.  I would like to
note that the number of monthly active users for
transportation alone is another 700,000 people.   There
may be similar technical
errors.  This mainly refers to
the fact that the dispatching system has not yet been fully implemented in the municipality.
Work is being done in that direction in the municipality. I
think there is
no unified management center yet.
If it is final, I
think there should be
no such problems.  I would also like to note that the
data that we receive and
analyze, since our
analysis is quite deep and
detailed, also based on the
current situation in the city, congestion, we
provide that data back in an already processed form to our partners, the Yerevan
Municipality, and
they, in turn,
display the data processed by us on those digital
billboards at the bus stop.
Then about the future, future plans,
any services that you think you
can add in Armenia and not only in
Armenia, and one more question, for example, do you
provide transportation within the country
, huh? In this case, taxi
services, delivery, etc., etc., are
there any plans to also provide interstate
transportation,
cargo transportation, passenger transportation? I can
say that from the perspective of passenger transportation,
it is a bit of a complicated issue.
I can give an example of
Armenia and Georgia.  There is
one law in Armenia regarding
taxi services, and another in Georgia, which means
that in fact,
whenever a driver who has the right to
pay the actual fees in Armenia and has the right to
provide such services
crosses the
Georgian border, he does not have the right to provide such services in Georgia.
For that, there
is a different legislative framework.  In Georgia, using the
example of Georgia, I can say that there are
two types of
licenses there. The license plate is
exclusively for white taxis
with a license plate number up to 10 years old [snorts], which have the right to
have that chessboard on them, they
also have the right to pick up people from the street,
etc.  It differs from one legislative field to another at
this time.  We had a
small experiment within the organization
related to cargo transportation,
not in Armenia, but in the
region under my jurisdiction
.  At the moment it
is an experiment, if this experiment
yields results, it is very possible that we will
also have some interest in
that part as well.
We have alternative means of transportation, for example, I think
last year it
made quite a stir that Armenia
was the first country where Yandex was
able to order a helicopter,
by the way, it uses that service,
yes, it uses it actively, look, after all,
helicopters are quite an expensive pleasure, it is
more frequent, but
yes, they also use it on its basis,
but it is not your helicopters, it is not another
service company, companies like
ours, companies like ours do
not own vehicles as such,
so it is always a partner who
has an appropriate vehicle, whether it
concerns a taxi, a
truck, because I don't know, for example,
I think not everyone knows that in Yandex
Delivery there is an
opportunity to order not only
regular deliveries, but also trucks of
various sizes, but
these are always vehicles belonging to our partners or
individuals
.  As for
new services, we
can say that on average we have two to three
new services a year. From the
latest
services released, I can say that we have
released our service
related to PowerBerry
rental.
Last year, we were quite active in the Yandex
advertising platform. It is a separate
platform aimed at B2B businesses
, which was released in the near future.
We have a gaming platform, Yandex
Games. It is a matter of a few days before it is
released. I really
hope that in the near future we
will be able to see robots that are part of our physics on the streets of Yerevan, which
will deal with acceleration. That is,
we
see some kind of box on wheels in different countries
and yes, it makes
deliveries,
and delivery via drones.
We are currently testing delivery via drones in
one of the countries in our region. Not
yet in Armenia.
Thank you for the conversation.
I talked to Aram Mkhitaryan at the business pavilion. Stay
healthy, we will meet.